<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. -->
    <string name="app_name">Alexandria Egypt</string>

    <!-- Category name for Restaurants. -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Category name for for Attractions. -->
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <!-- Category name for Museums. -->
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>

    <!-- Category name for Cafes. -->
    <string name="category_cafes">Cafes</string>

    <!-- Description of the images. -->
    <string name="the_image_is_magnified">The image is magnified</string>
    <string name="the_image_of_the_place">The image of the place</string>

    <!-- Names of Restaurants. -->
    <string name="seagull">Seagull</string>
    <string name="hosny_grill">Hosny Grill</string>
    <string name="balbaa">Balbaa</string>
    <string name="kadoura">Kadoura</string>
    <string name="abo_faris">Abo Faris</string>
    <string name="tikka">Tikka</string>
    <string name="ibn_el_balad">Ibn El balad</string>
    <string name="sultan_ayoub">sultan ayoub</string>

    <!-- Addresses of Restaurants. -->
    <string name="seagull_address">Gleem – Highest Café Latino</string>
    <string name="hosny_grill_address">Extension of Suez Canal St, beside International Park Alex</string>
    <string name="balbaa_address">El Moushir St,beside Armed Forces Hospital, Sidi Gaber</string>
    <string name="kadoura_address">33 Beiram El Tounisy St,Bahary</string>
    <string name="abo_faris_address">242 El Guish RD, Roushdy</string>
    <string name="tikka_address">El Guish Rd, beside Egyptian Sea Scout Club, Bahary</string>
    <string name="ibn_el_balad_address">El Horreya Rd, inside Alexandria Sporting Club</string>
    <string name="sultan_ayoub_address">inside San Stafano Grand Plaza Mall</string>

    <!-- Names of Attractions. -->
    <string name="maamoura">Maamoura</string>
    <string name="montazah">Montazah</string>
    <string name="citadel_of_qaitbay">Citadel of Qaitbay</string>
    <string name="stanly_bridge">Stanly Bridge</string>
    <string name="green_plaza">Green Plaza</string>
    <string name="san_stefano_mall">San Stefano Mall</string>
    <string name="carrefour">Carrefour</string>
    <string name="planetarium_science_center">Planetarium Science Center</string>
    <string name="bibliotheca_alexandrina">Bibliotheca Alexandrina</string>
    <string name="san_giovanni">San Giovanni</string>

    <!-- Addresses of Attractions. -->
    <string name="maamoura_address">About 1km east of Montazah</string>
    <string name="montazah_address">El Mandara Bahery, Qasm El Montaza</string>
    <string name="citadel_of_qaitbay_address">Qaitbay St., El Anfoushi</string>
    <string name="stanly_bridge_address">near the city centre of Alexandria</string>
    <string name="green_plaza_address">14th Of May Rd., Semouha</string>
    <string name="san_stefano_mall_address">El Guish Rd., San Stephano</string>
    <string name="carrefour_address">Gate 4 1St, Alexandria Cairo Desert Road</string>
    <string name="planetarium_science_center_address">El Guish Rd., El Shatby</string>
    <string name="bibliotheca_alexandrina_address">El Guish Rd., El Shatby</string>
    <string name="san_giovanni_address">205 El-Gaish Rd, Stanley Bridge</string>

    <!-- Names of Museums. -->
    <string name="royal_jewelry_museum">Royal Jewelry Museum</string>
    <string name="alexandria_aquarium">Alexandria Aquarium</string>
    <string name="thegrecoroman_museum">The Greco-Roman Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_of_fine_arts">Museum of Fine Arts</string>
    <string name="alexandria_national_museum">Alexandria National Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_of_calligraphy">Museum of Calligraphy</string>
    <string name="the_sadat_museum">The Sadat Museum</string>
    <string name="cavafy_museum">Cavafy Museum</string>

    <!-- Addresses of Museums. -->
    <string name="royal_jewelry_museum_address">27 Ahmed Yehia Pasha St., Zizinia</string>
    <string name="alexandria_aquarium_address">Qaitbay St., EL ANFOUSHI</string>
    <string name="thegrecoroman_museum_address">5 el Mathaf St</string>
    <string name="museum_of_fine_arts_address">1 Menasha St. Moharram Bey</string>
    <string name="alexandria_national_museum_address">131 El-Shaheed Galal El-Desouky, Bab Sharqi</string>
    <string name="museum_of_calligraphy_address">6 Menasha St. Moharram Bey</string>
    <string name="the_sadat_museum_address">Port Said St., El shatby, inside Bibliotheca Alexandrina</string>
    <string name="cavafy_museum_address">6 Sharm El Sheikh St. Off Istanbul St. Raml Station</string>

    <!-- Names of Cafes. -->
    <string name="zanillis">Zanilli\'s</string>
    <string name="paplo">Paplo</string>
    <string name="costa">Costa</string>
    <string name="santos">Santos</string>
    <string name="carlos">Carlos</string>
    <string name="latino">Latino</string>
    <string name="delight">Delight</string>
    <string name="roastery">Roastery</string>

    <!-- Addresses of Cafes. -->
    <string name="zanillis_address">Montaza Palace Gardens</string>
    <string name="paplo_address">Kournish, Stanly, Highest Supreem Cafe</string>
    <string name="costa_address">274 El Guish Rd, Stanly</string>
    <string name="santos_address">El-Gaish Road, Qism Sidi Gabir</string>
    <string name="carlos_address">424 Kournish st, Loran</string>
    <string name="latino_address">El Guish Rd, Gleem</string>
    <string name="delight_address">37 El Fardous St., Semouha</string>
    <string name="roastery_address">38 Abdel Qader Ragab St, Roushdy</string>

    <string name="description1">The Royal Jewelry Museum (Arabic: متحف المجوهرات‎) is an art and history museum in the Zizenia neighborhood of Alexandria, Egypt. It is located in the former palace of Princess Fatma Al-Zahra\'. The building\'s halls contain an inestimable collection of jewels and jewelry of the Muhammad Ali Dynasty. 19th-century paintings, statues, and decorative arts are also exhibited in the rooms and lobbies. The museum was first inaugurated on 24 October 1986. After several years of renovations and expansion it was reopened in April 2010</string>
    <string name="description2">Alexandria Aquarium is a small aquarium in Alexandria, Egypt. It was built in 1930 and is near Qaitbay fort on Alexandria\'s Eastern Harbour. The aquarium exhibits many species from the Mediterranean and Red Seas around Egypt, as well as some freshwater species from the Nile and the Amazon. Animals on display range from fish to crustaceans and turtles (both marine and freshwater). The Aquarium is also home to the Marine Research Institute..</string>
    <string name="description3">The Graeco-Roman Museum is an archaeological museum located in Alexandria, Egypt. Erected in 1892, it was first built in a five-room apartment, inside one small building on Rosetta Street (later Avenue Canope and now Horriya). In 1895, it was transferred to another, larger building near Gamal Abdul Nasser Street. The museum contains several pieces dating from the Graeco-Roman (Ptolemaic) era in the 3rd century BC, such as a sculpture of Apis in black granite, the sacred bull of the Egyptians, mummies, sarcophagus, tapestries, and other objects offering a view of Greco-Roman civilization in contact with ancient Egypt.</string>
    <string name="description4">The Alexandria Museum of Fine Arts is a museum for Egyptian and Middle-Eastern fine art situated in the Moharam Bek neighborhood of Alexandria, Egypt. It houses a collection of works by Egyptian artist and a selection of works from Baroque, Romanticism, Rococo and Orientalism. In addition, noteworthy examples of carving, printing and sculpture from Egyptian and European artists. The museum aims to promote art to the local community and to a greater extent Egyptian society, through a selection of activities: art workshops, exhibitions and museum education for children; exhibitions for noted Egyptian artists and international cultural exchange activities.</string>
    <string name="description5">The Alexandria National Museum (ANM) is a museum in Alexandria, Egypt. It was inaugurated the 31 December 2003[1] by Hosni Mubarak and it is located in a renovated Italian style palace in Tariq Al-Horreya Street (former Rue Fouad). The building used to be home to the United States consulate.</string>
    <string name="description6">Egyptian Culture Minister Abdel-Wahed El Nabawy inaugurated the Museum of Arabic Calligraphy at the Fine Arts Museum in Alexandria on August 22nd, 2015. The museum houses a collection of modern and ancient masterpieces created by artists who specialized in Arabic calligraphy and its unique decorative qualities. It also houses a collection of rare Arabic manuscripts and paintings by some of the world’s most famous calligraphers and pioneers of the art form, adding up to an unprecedented collection for a calligraphy museum.</string>
    <string name="description7">The Sadat Museum is a cultural museum in Alexandria, Egypt, dedicated to the legacy of Egyptian president Anwar Al Sadat. It was inaugurated on February 17, 2009 by Suzanne Mubarak and Jehan Al Sadat and is located next to the planetarium of the Bibliotheca Alexandrina, encompassing 200 square meters. The museum also launched an internet website that contains videos, images and documents about Sadat. The Museum holds the military uniform Sadat was wearing when he was assassinated, his desk, radio and some of the swords he received from Arab countries. The web collection contains 14,000 images and 61 hours of video.</string>
    <string name="description8">Cavafy Museum is an apartment museum in center Alexandria, Egypt, formerly was the residence place of Greek poet Constantine P.Cavafy where he lived most of his life. The apartment is located near Cairo Opera House in Alexandria, in Attarin area. The street name was Lepsius during Cavafy\'s life, it was renamed Sharm El Sheikh, then after the museum was opened, the narrow and short street became Cavafy Street, which is quite close to two of the city\'s most important streets, Fouad St. and Saffiya Zagholul St.</string>
    <string name="map">map</string>

</resources>

